[
    {
        "numb": 1,
        "question": "  The Visual Basic Code Editor will automatically detect certain types of errors as you are entering code.? ",
        "answer": " True",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
            
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 2,
        "question": "Keywords are also referred to as reserved words ?",
        "answer": "True",
        "options": [
            "True",
            "False"
            
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 3,
        "question": " When the user clicks a button, _________ is triggered?",
        "answer": "an event",
        "options": [
            "an event",
            "a method",
            "a setting",
            "a property"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 4,
        "question": "What property of controls tells the order they receive the focus when the tab key is pressed during run time?",
        "answer": "Tab index ",
        "options": [
            "Focus order",
            "Focus number",
            "Tab index",
            "Control order"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 5,
        "question": "Sizing Handles make it very easy to resize virtually any control when developing applications with Visual Basic. When working in the Form Designer, how are these sizing handles displayed?",
        "answer": "A rectangle with small squares around your control.",
        "options": [
            "A 3-D outline around your control.",
            "A rectangle with small squares around your control.",
            "A rectangle with 4 arrows, one in each corner, around your control. ",
            "None of the above."
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 6,
        "question": "When creating a new application in Visual Basic, you are asked to supply a name for the program. If you do not specify a name, a default name is XXXXX XXXXX is this default name?",
        "answer": "C+B",
        "options": [
            "Wapplication followed by a number. ",
            "Application followed by a number",
			"WindowsApplication.",
            "C+B"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 7,
        "question": "Which of the properties in a control’s list of properties is used to give the control a meaningful name?",
        "answer": "Name",
        "options": [
            "Text",
            "ContextMenu",
            "ControlName",
            "Name"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 8,
        "question": "Pseudocode is? ",
        "answer": "a description of an algorithm similar to a computer language.",
        "options": [
            "data that have been encoded for security.",
            "a description of an algorithm similar to a computer language.",
			"a program that doesn’t work.",
            "the incorrect results of a computer program."
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 9,
        "question": " The value returned by InputBox is a string.?",
        "answer": "True",
        "options": [
           "True",
           "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 10,
        "question": "A variable declared outside of an event procedure is said to have class-level scope.?",
        "answer": "True",
        "options": [
           "True",
           "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 11,
        "question": " What is the correct statement when declaring and assigning the value of 100 to an Integer variable called numPeople?",
        "answer": "Dim numPeople As Integer = 100 ",
        "options": [
            "Dim numPeople =",
            "Dim numPeople = Int(100) ",
            "numPeople = 100",
            "Dim numPeople As Integer = 100 "
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 12,
        "question": "What value will be assigned to the numeric variable x when the following statement is executed? x = 2 + 3 * 4",
        "answer": "14",
        "options": [
            "28",
            "22",
            "14",
            "228"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 13,
        "question": "Which of the following is a valid name for a variable?",
        "answer": "Two_One",
        "options": [
            "Two_One",
            "2One",
            "Two One",
            "Two.One"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 14,
        "question": "Keywords in Visual Basic are words that",
        "answer": "have special meaning and should not be used when naming variables",
        "options": [
            "should be used when naming variables",
            "are used to name controls, such as TextBox1, Command2, etc",
            "have special meaning and should not be used when naming variables",
            "are used as prefixes for control names (such as txt, btn, lbl, and lst)"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 15,
        "question": "What is the proper syntax when using a message dialog box? .",
        "answer": "MessageBox.Show(“Hi there”, “Hi”)",
        "options": [
            "MessageBox.Show(“Hi there”, “Hi”)",
            "MessageBox.Show(Hi there, Hi) ",
			"MessageBox.Show “Hi There”, “Hi”",
            "MessageBox.Show Hi There, Hi"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 16,
        "question": "What will be the output of the following statement? txtBox.Text = FormatCurrency(1234.567)?",
        "answer": "$1,234.57",
        "options": [
            "$1234.567",
            "1,234.57",
            "$1234.57",
            "$1,234.57"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 17,
        "question": "The following lines of code are correct. If age >= 13 And < 20 Then txtOutput.Text = “You are a teenager.” End If? ",
        "answer": "False",
        "options": [
           "True",
           "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 18,
        "question": "Given that x = 7, y = 2, and z = 4, the following If block will display “TRUE”. If (x > y) Or (y > z) Then txtBox.Text = “TRUE” End If?",
        "answer": "True",
        "options": [
           "True",
           "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 19,
        "question": "Asc(“A”) is 65. What is Asc(“C”)??",
        "answer": "68 ",
        "options": [
            "66",
            "67  ",
            "68",
            "79 "
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 20,
        "question": "Asc(“A”) is 65. What is displayed by txtBox.Text = Chr(65) & “BC”?",
        "answer": "ABC",
        "options": [
            "ABC",
            "A BC",
            "656667",
            "Not enough information is available"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 21,
        "question": "Which of the following expressions has as its value the words “Hello World? surrounded by quotation marks?",
        "answer": "data sheet",
        "options": [
            "work sheet",
            "chart sheet",
			"module sheet",
            "data sheet"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 22,
        "question": "When a range is selected, how can you activate the previous cell?",
        "answer": "“Hello World”",
        "options": [
            "“Hello World”",
            "Chr(34) & “Hello World”",
            "Chr(34) & Hello World & Chr(34)",
			"Chr(34) & “Hello World” & Chr(34)"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 23,
        "question": "Which of the following is a valid Visual Basic conditional statement?",
        "answer": "(2 < n) Or (n < 5)",
        "options": [
            "2 < n < 5",
            "2 < n Or < 5 ",
            "2 < n Or 5 ",
            "(2 < n) Or (n < 5)"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 24,
        "question": "The three main logical operators are ________, _________, and ________.",
        "answer": "And, Or, Not ",
        "options": [
            "And, Or, Not ",
            "And, Not, If",
            "Or, Not, If",
            "False, And, True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 25,
        "question": "Which value for x would make the following condition true: (x >= 5) And (x <= 6)",
        "answer": " B+C",
        "options": [
            "x is equal to 7",
            "x is equal to 5",
			"x is equal to 5.001",
            "B+C"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 26,
        "question": "Suppose that the selector in a Select Case block is the string variable myVar. Which of the following is NOT a valid Case clause?",
        "answer": "Case myVar.Length",
        "options": [
            "Case “Adams”",
            "Case “739”",
			"Case (myVar.Substring(0, 1)",
            "Case myVar.Length"
        ]
    },
    {
        "numb": 27,
        "question": "Which Case clause will be true whenever the value of the selector in a Select Case block is greater than or equal to 7?",
        "answer": "Case Is >= 7",
        "options": [
            "Case Is >7",
            "Case Is = 8 ",
            "Case Is >= 7",
            "Case Is <= 8"
        ]
    }
   ]